yourtherapysource.com 2019-12-19

# Your Therapy Source Privacy Policy - Your Therapy Source

### Your Therapy Source, Inc.  Privacy Policy 

_Last Updated: April 18, 2018_

This Privacy Policy describes how and when we collect, use and share your information when you visit our website and purchase our products.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated within and subject to the definitions established in the Terms of Service.

* * *

Collection and Use of Information

Information is collected from you when you fill out and submit a form or register on our website to receive information or purchase products. When filling out a form or registering on our website, when applicable, you may be asked to provide personally identifiable information. You may, however, visit our website anonymously.

Your personal data may be shared with third parties that Your Therapy Source Inc. works with, like billing and payment processing services, communications and content delivery, etc. We only share data with third parties that comply with their applicable data protection laws.

* * *

Purpose of Collecting Your Information 

The information we collect from you may be used to process transactions.  If you provide us with your email, the email address you have provided may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

* * *

Protecting Your Information 

We implement a number of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you have registered on our website to use certain Services, including the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those individuals authorized with special access rights to such systems and subject to the obligation to keep the information confidential.  After the completion of a financial transaction, associated information will not be stored on our servers.

* * *

Use of Cookies 

We may use cookies to collect website usage data for analytical purposes and to improve user experience. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer’s hard disk. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. By changing the settings in your browser, you may disallow the acceptance of cookies. If you disallow cookies, some aspects of our website may not function properly. 

* * *

Sharing and Disclosure of Information 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include information shared or disclosed at your direction or information shared or disclosed to trusted third parties who assist us in operation of our website, conducting our day-to-day business, or directly servicing you, subject to confidentiality obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy, and on the condition that the third parties use your private personal data only on our behalf and pursuant to our instructions.

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our website policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

In the event that Your Therapy Source, Inc. is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this Privacy Policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity.

* * *

Changes To Your Personal Information 

If you have registered on our website to purchase our products, we provide you access to tools that enable you to access or make changes to the personal information you have provided to us. You can also permanently delete your account by emailing us at contactus@yourtherapysource.com.

* * *

Our Privacy Policy Toward Children Under 13 

Our website and products are not directed to persons under 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at contactus@yourtherapysource.com. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child’s account.

* * *

Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

* * *

Terms of Service 

Please also visit our Terms of Service section, which governs the use of our website.

* * *

Your Consent 

By using our website, you consent to our online privacy policy.

* * *

Changes to our Privacy Policy 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

* * *

California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [contactus@yourtherapysource.com](mailto:contactus@yourtherapysource.com)

> Your Therapy Source, Inc.
> 
> 43 South Main Street
> 
> Schaghticoke, NY 12154

Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83(c)(2), Your Therapy Source, Inc. does not share personal information with third parties for direct marketing purposes.

If you are a California resident under the age of 18, and a registered user of any website where this policy is posted, California Business and Professions Code Section 22581 permits you to request and obtain removal of content or information you have publicly posted. To make such a request, please send an email with a detailed description of the specific content or information to contactus@yourtherapysource.com. Please be aware that such a request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information you have posted and that there may be circumstances in which the law does not require or allow removal even if requested.

* * *

Contacting Us 

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

> 
> Your Therapy Source Inc.
> 
> 43 South Main Street
> 
> Schaghticoke, NY 12154

 _This Privacy Policy was last modified on the April 18, 2018 and is effective immediately._
